(Sheldon:)My apologies.
(Sheldon:)I would've been here sooner but the bus
kept stopping for other people to get on it.
(Amy:)I saved you a dumpling.
(Sheldon:)Oh. Your concern for me is touching.
(Sheldon:)It will serve you well
when you take me to the dentist tomorrow.
(Amy:)I'm sorry, Sheldon, I'm busy. I'm right
in the middle of my addiction study.
(Amy:)I've got a lab full of alcoholic monkeys,
and tomorrow we switch them to O'Doul's.
You're my girIfriend and
you're not going to cater to my every need?
(Sheldon:)Oh, where'd the magic go?
(Penny:)Sheldon, that's not
what girIfriends are for.
AIthough, you don't use them
for what they're for, so what do I know?
(Bernadette:)Howard doesn't make me
do his shopping, take him to the dentist...
(Bernadette:)- ...or pick up his dry cleaning, right?
- Absolutely. But when Ma's hips give out...
(Howard:)...you're up, kid.
Well, if Amy's too busy, it gives the rest of
you an opportunity to make my life easier...